{
    "question": "Contoh percakapan 6 orang di dalam hotel dalam bahasa inggris",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "Receptionist: Good morning! Welcome to Cozy Hotel. Could I help you?<br>Mr. John : Good morning! I&#039;d like to book a room for several days, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. How many days would you like to stay?<br>Mrs. John : 3 days and 2 nights, please<br>Receptionist : Certainly. We&#039;ve got room 145, 209, 310 for free. which one do you prefer?<br>Lily: Dad, I think I prefer room 310<br>Dave: Me too, dad<br>Mr. john: ok, then we&#039;d like to book room 310, please<br>Receptionist: Certainly, sir. How are you going to be paying?<br>Mrs. John: Credit card, please<br>Receptionist: Sure. Is there anything else we could help?<br>Mr. John: I think we need someone to help us bring our luggage<br>Receptionist: Sure. We&#039;ve got bellboy to help you<br>Bellboy: Good morning! <br>Mrs &amp; Mr John: Good morning! Could you help us with our luggage to room 310<br>Bellboy: Sure.<br>Receptionist: We hope you&#039;ll enjoy your stay here<br>Mrs. John: We hope so. Thank you<br>Receptionist: Your welcome<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "buatkan-naskah-drama-bahasa-inggris-untuk-7-orang-cewek-4-orang-581",
            "question": "buatkan Naskah drama bahasa inggris untuk 7 orang. cewek 4 orang, cwok 3 orang....\r\ntolong :)\u00a0 bebas, tpi jangan pnjng.panjang",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Kiki: Hello,Good Morning all\nTerusin Aja yah Tema nasjah englus itu yg bagus best friend in my heart",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "create-dialogs-based-on-the-situations-below-situations-1-you-a-323",
            "question": "Create dialogs based on the situations below    situations 1 : you are at farewell party at your school. a friend has just finished singing a song well. you offer compliment to her. and she rejects the compliment. what do you and your friend say?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>me\u00a0 : your song was so amazing <br>him : thank you again <br>me\u00a0 : we&#039;ll split up .... <br>him : yes ... but I hope we&#039;ll meet again someday <br>me\u00a0 : I too ..... <br>him : I&#039;ll see you again, you have to promise we will meet again <br>me\u00a0 : yea ... I promise you, and someday we will meet again</span><br><br>arti:<br>aku : lagumu tadi sangat menakjubkan<br>dia\u00a0 : terima kasih kembali<br>aku : kita akan berpisah....<br>dia\u00a0 : ya...tapi aku harap kita akan bertemu lagi suatu saat nanti<br>aku : aku juga.....<br>dia\u00a0 : sampai jumpa lagi,kau harus berjanji kita akan bertemu lagi<br>aku : ya...aku berjanji,dan suatu saat nanti kita bakal ketemu lagi<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-kalimat-active-passive-pada-present-simple-past-simple-p-261",
            "question": "Contoh kalimat active passive pada present simple, past simple, present cont, dan past cont!:)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Simple Present Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncall my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am called by my best friend<br>Simple Past Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\ncalled my friend yesterday\n<br>\n-Passive :\nI was called by my best friend yesterday\n\n<br>Present\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nam calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI am being called by my best friend<br>\u00a0Past\nContinous Tense<br>\u00a0-Active : I\nwas calling my best friend<br>\u00a0-Passive :\nI was being called by my best friend\n\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kalau-nama-lain-dari-v1-v2-v3-dan-ving-apa-701",
            "question": "Kalau nama lain dari V1, V2, V3, dan Ving apa?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "v1 : bare infintive<br>v2 : past tense<br>v3: past participle<br>ve/es : additional infinitive<br>ving : present participle<br><br>maksudnya ini ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "speech-contest-terjemahan-bahasa-indonesianya-adalah-885",
            "question": "Speech contest terjemahan bahasa indonesianya adalah....",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "speech contest = kompetisi pidato<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "maksudnya itu artinya dalam bahasa indonesia yah?<br><br>Dalam bahasa indonesia artinya :\u00a0lomba pidato<br><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "sebutkan-lagu-yang-liriknya-lagunya-dominan-mengandung-if-clause-720",
            "question": "Sebutkan lagu yang liriknya lagunya dominan mengandung \"if clause\" atau \"Conditional sentences\"?    #selain Beyonce-If i were a boy",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Lagu-lagu yang liriknya mengandung dominan mengandung If Clause atau Conditional Sentence\n</strong></p><p><strong>1.\tIf You Are Not The One \u2013 Daniel Bedingfield\n</strong></p><p><strong>2.\tDear Future Husband \u2013 Meghan Trainor\n</strong></p><p><strong>3.\tWhat If \u2013 Simple Plan\n</strong></p><p><strong>4.\tIf I Let You Go \u2013 Westlife\n</strong></p><p><strong>5.\tI Would \u2013 Justin Bieber\n</strong></p><p><strong>6.\tIf Only \u2013 The Hoobastank\n</strong></p><p><strong>7.\tIf Tomorrow Never Comes \u2013 Ronan Keating\n</strong></p><p><strong>8.\tIf I Lose Myself \u2013 OneRepublic\n</strong></p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>If Clause atau Conditional sentence merupakan jenis kalimat dalam bahasa inggris yang digunakan untuk menyatakan pengandaian terhadap sesuatu yang dapat terjadi apabila kejadian lain terjadi.\n</p><p>\n</p><h3>Jenis-jenis Conditional Sentence\n</h3><p><strong>1.\tConditional Sentence Type 1\n</strong></p><p>Jenis conditional sentence yang digunakan untuk menyatakan pengandaian terhadap suatu kejadian di masa kini yang masih dapat terjadi di masa depan.\n</p><p>Struktur kalimat: If + simple present tense + simple future tense\n</p><p>Contoh: If I have time tonight, I will watch a movie.\n</p><p>\n</p><p><strong>2.\tConditional Sentence Type 2\n</strong></p><p>Jenis conditional sentence yang digunakan untuk menyatakan pengandaian terhadap suatu kejadian di masa kini, namun tidak memiliki kemungkinan terjadi. Jenis conditional sentence ini paling umum digunakan.\n</p><p>Struktur kalimat: If + simple past tense + simple past future tense\n</p><p>Contoh: If I didn\u2019t wake up late, I would not miss the bus.\n</p><p>\n</p><p><strong>3.\tConditional Sentence Type 3\n</strong></p><p>Jenis conditional sentence yang digunakan untuk menyatakan pengandaian terhadap sesuatu yang terjadi di masa lampau.\n</p><p>Struktur kalimat: If + past perfect tense + past future perfect tense/past future perfect continuous tense\n</p><p>Contoh: If I had taken the scholarship, I would have been studying in New York.\n</p><p>\n</p><p>Semoga membantu.\n</p><p>\n</p><p><strong>Pelajari lebih lanjut\n</strong></p><p>Materi tentang if clause https://brainly.co.id/tugas/16714249\n</p><p>Contoh karangan yang menggunakan if clause https://brainly.co.id/tugas/37253799\n</p><p>Contoh kalimat if clause brainly.co.id/tugas/12473246\n</p><p>\n</p><p><strong>Detil Jawaban\n</strong></p><p>Kelas: XII\n</p><p>Mata Pelajaran: Bahasa Inggris\n</p><p>Bab: Grammar\n</p><p>Kode Kategori: 12.5.3\n</p><p>\n</p><p>#AyoBelajar\n</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "ada-yang-bisa-kasi-masukan-judul-fairy-tale-legenda-dan-fabel-916",
            "question": "ada yang bisa kasi masukan judul fairy tale, legenda, dan fabel? masing - masing 5 kakak :\"D Terimakasih",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "menurut aku....<br>fairy tale: pinnochio, cinderella, alice in the wonderland(rada fabel dikit ini ), tinkerbell,snow white, frozen, the little mermaid, dll princess2 gitu deh bisa disebut fairy tale<br>legenda: malin kundang, dsb lah yg gituan pkonya<br>fabel: si kancil, bugs bunny, tom and jerry, dll yang pokonya ttg binatang yang bisa berbicara seperti manusia:)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Fiary Tale : The Prince of Frog, Cinderella, Beauty and The Beast, Sleeping Beauty, Snow White<br>Legenda :\u00a0 Malin Kundang, Sangkuriang, Roro Jonggrang, Lake Toba, Kang Kabayan<br>Fabel : Kancil and The Giant Story, The King Kinka, Kancil and The Tiger, Kancil and Crocodile, The Rock and The Weasel<br>Semoga membantu ^_^<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pengertian-globalisasi-dalam-bahasa-inggris-457",
            "question": "Pengertian globalisasi dalam bahasa inggris..",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>the change when the world feels so near. because we can get much and easy connection with other people in aroud the world. it&#039;s so easy.. and it help the development proccess of culture,lifestyle. from the side of attitude. globalization can make peoples being consumtive, it will create the bad attitude like egoist, prestige,ignore ,esteem. so that, therefore globalization can make the positive, negative effect ,but thats depend on us how the way you are to face globalization</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "pelajaran-bahasa-inggris-unit-6-kurikulum-2013-activity-9-dan-282",
            "question": "Pelajaran bahasa inggris, unit 6, kurikulum 2013, activity 9 dan activity 10",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "A : hello Dewi. Is kaisar here?<br>B : No. i\u2019m afraid he go\u00a0out\u00a0<br>A : oh, what a pity ! when exactly does he go<br><span>B : about fifteen minutes ago<br></span><br>2. A : your hair looks different. do you have a haircut?\u00a0<br>B : yes, i have<br>A : do you cut it yourself?\u00a0<br><span>B : no, kadita cut it for me\u00a0<br></span><br>Klo salah maaf atau kamu\u00a0udah bisa jawab ?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "persamaan-simple-past-amp-present-perfect-695",
            "question": "Persamaan simple past &amp; present perfect",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "sama sama merupakan absolute relative tenses dimana sebuah kalimat terdiri dari lebih dari satu keterangan waktu.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "sama-sama menceritakan tentang masa lampau<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}